milbergweissjustice.com 2006-11-24

# Milberg Weiss Justice

Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy Statement is applicable to www.milbergweiss.com, www.hmosettlements.com, www.ipofraud.com and all other Web sites on the World Wide Web owned or operated by Milberg Weiss Bershad & Schulman LLP ("Milberg Weiss"). 

Milberg Weiss does not collect personal information from you except in the following instances: 

* Information your web browser software may automatically provide to our web servers, such as the address of the Web site you linked from, the identity of your Internet Service Provider, and the type and version of the browser you are using; 

* Information you provide to us in an e-mail message or attachment; and 

* Information you provide to us in a form on our Web site. 

Any information you submit to us will only be used for the purpose for which it was submitted. 

A "cookie" is a small electronic file that may be written to your hard drive by a Web site you are visiting. Milberg Weiss uses a single cookie with its Web site. The cookie contains a short unique alphanumeric string so that we may recognize a specific user. There is no personal information contained in this cookie. We use cookies to: 

* Improve privacy by storing information a user may submit to us on our secure server and referencing it with a cookie. This enables us to transmit user information in a secure manner; 

* Keep track of user requests to search and sort through information on the site; 

* Personalize the site for our users. For example, certain confirmation pages may display the name users provide to us; and 

* Provide administrative services. 

If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the settings in your browser that will turn off the use of cookies. If you choose to turn off cookies, it is possible that some areas of the Web site will not function properly. Please refer to the Help function of your browser for specific information on how to turn off cookies. 

Milberg Weiss reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location. 

Last updated on May 1, 2004. If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us.
